back.
>> It feels amazing. I felt like I never
left, you know. It feels like home, you
know. I felt welcome when I walked in
these two doors this morning. Uh it's
amazing. The energy is unmatched and,
you know, uh the atmosphere here is just
amazing.
>> What how are you different as a player?
Where can you help them more than even
what you were able to before? Um, you
know, obviously, you know, I was a I
feel like a key rotational piece when I
was here last time, but I feel like I'm
I'm going to be able to add more force,
you know, especially with the interior
and helping this everybody out. You
know, my my goal is to disrupt the game
and to help people disrupt the game. So,
you know, I feel like that that kind of
factors into everything as far as, you
know, uh overall defensive play. So, you
know, uh my key thing is to be
destructive here and help everybody
around be destructive to help everybody
else at every level of defense.
>> Thanks, Tim.
>> Nikki.
>> Hi, Tim. Um, how much different does the
organization seem just, you know,
physically in the building just with all
the new people? I mean, how much
different is it than when you left?
>> It's amazing. I I feel like things
definitely uh had an upside. You know,
things changed for the better. you know,
uh this just the the resources that's
here now and you know, uh definitely I
see a change on how things were and how
it looks now. And you know, I I would
definitely say it's for the better. You
know, I definitely I feel like it's a uh
a healed environment.
>> And what what are your early impressions
of Dante Jones? I don't know if you've
had time to meet with him yet, but
>> it's energy. You know, uh, you know,
coach coach, I I like coaches that, you
know, it's all about energy and, you
know, it's it's just like playing chess.
You know, when you got a D coordinator
that's that's uh that that knows how to
play chess at a high level and, you
know, that knows how to use his weapons
and and pieces, you know, the sky's is
the limit. You know, I love the energy
he brings and I know he's going to be
versatile as far as how we play defense
and I know he's going to lot let us get
after it.
Liam,
>> hi Tim. I'm just curious with all the
moves they've made on the defensive
line, you're not the only signing they
made. How does it feel for you to come
in to a kind of overhauled group where a
lot of the people haven't played
together um at the NFL level?
>> Uh it feels amazing. You know,
obviously, you know, uh every team's
going to be different every year. So
obviously uh having that uh initial
thought in my back of my head is is is
something but you know it's all about
how we how we come together you know how
we uh how we practice together and you
know it's it's all about building
togetherness and uh having unity on and
off the field you know I feel like uh
when you're with with a group of guys
it's not just uh football it got to be
everything got to be life and you know I
feel like that's one thing I bring uh
entertainment you know I'm an
entertainer uh I bring love joy and you
know a good energy uh to my work
environment. So, I feel like that's
going to help contribute to the to to
the whole locker room.
>> And what made Washington the right fit
now? Was it the coaching staff, the new
scheme, the you know, the financials?
Like, what was it that made now the
right time to come back home? Um,
obviously, you know, I was here, I got
drafted here, you know, I was here, uh,
I seen a front office change, you know,
uh, I seen things clear up, but, you
know, it's I'm from I'm from Manasses,
Virginia. You know, uh, I I grew up a
Washington fan. You know, uh, I grew up,
uh, uh, cheering for this organization.
You know, uh, I feel like when I left, I
didn't like how I left. You know, I feel
like, you know, this is I ain't gonna
say this is redeem, but this is like a
new era, new chapter. So, I I definitely
feel like, you know, this time around
with the new coaching staff and the new
uh front office, uh this is this is this
is the environment that I want to be in.
>> Anna,
>> hey Tim. Uh welcome back to Washington
second time around. Uh do you know any
of your teammates and coming back to
Washington uh now?
>> Yeah, I already have them. Uh we got
Trustway. Shout out to my boy uh Jay
Reeves. We got uh Terry, scary Terry,
and we got Big Pain. I remember
everybody. You uh I already kind of uh
reconnected with Pain, you know, but I
can't wait to see all my other guys, you
know. Uh nothing's changed. I'm just
older.
>> And and they they preach a lot about the
brotherhood here in Washington. And you
talked about you bring your
entertainment flavor, your love, and
your joy and everything. How do you
think you fit even more so into this
brotherhood?
>> Well, I'm the brother and this is the
hood. So, I mean,
so that that's how we going to go about
it often. But, you know, I'm uh I'm I'm
I'm one of the I'm adjustable. You know,
I feel like I I I adapt in any kind of
environment, you know. Uh I feel like
that's one of the big things about me
when I have teammates in the past. You
know, you're going to hear me before you
see me. And uh you just I'm just all
energy, you I feel like, you know, if
you could bring good energy to your work
environment, you can have good results.
So, that's just is my that's been my
thing going into year nine. And I'm just
excited.
>> Welcome back again. Thanks.
>> Thank you.
>> Hey Tim, also welcome back uh to town.
Um with regard, what was it in terms of
like playing? What did they kind of sell
you on as ter role? I know it's evolving
with the new defensive coordinator, but
what did they kind of sell you on the
role and how they kind of saw you
fitting in?
>> However they wanted me to, I'm I'm
interchangeable. So, I mean, uh, however
they want to use me, I'm I'm here, you
know, if if if that's the play, no. Is
that the play three? If they want me to
line up outside, I could do it all. But
I I I'm coming to to
control the middle of the field, I I
would say. But, you know, um I'm
definitely looking forward to I think
I'm going to be uh used in a a really
good way. And I feel like I'm going to
be used definitely to help the defense,
you know, just uh being being able to
penetrate and do what and do what I've
been doing the past like my career. Just
being able to be involved and just cause
havoc and just being able to destruct
plays every play and just being able to
just to be a force.
>> And you talked about the changes. What
do you think of the Did you get lost in
the locker room like the rest of us the
first time?
>> I don't even think I seen a locker room
yet, but you know uh
>> Well, then you're for surprise.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But, uh it's I love the
changes though, you know. Uh the weight
room, you know, uh the nutrition area,
you know, uh I haven't seen everything
yet. I haven't even been in the training
room, but this just I'm I'm loving the
new eye and, you know, I'm loving what
they're doing with the place.
>> Thanks,
>> Blake.
Welcome back, Tim. when you said uh you
know nothing's changed. Well, the the
hair on you's changed up there with the
with the dread. So, uh welcome back. You
know, when you left, you said this is
kind of like a chance for you to redeem
some things and you know, so when you
left and you went to Buffalo and you see
this team get to the NFC Championship
game, you know, what how did that make
you feel? And then also, how important
is it for you to be back now to get them
over the hump to get to a Super Bowl? Uh
what I seen in changes, you know, uh
obviously, you know, it's been a while
since Washington. I think I don't know
in the last time Washington's been in
the playoffs. I my last year in
Washington, we made the playoffs. Uh
but, you know, I just feel like uh
the the change
I just feel like uh I don't know.
I just feel like the change in I I lost
your question. I'm so sorry.
So, no, just just just, you know, when
you went to Buffalo and then you see
this team get to an NFC championship
game, you know, reach heights that they
had never really reached, especially
when you were there, you know. So, how
important is it for you now to be back
to kind of get them over the hump to get
to that Super Bowl?
>> Well, uh, first of all, this, uh, when I
was here, we made the playoffs. made it
playoffs like six and like I don't know
we we didn't really win that many uh
games but you know just seeing them
going to the playoffs winning 10 plus
games and being able and just this this
every week in and out week in and out
you know it just it just tells that the
culture has changed and you know uh it
just shows that you know that they're
about winning you know they got the
right guys in here you know they got the
right guys upstairs and the the mindset
towards everything is winning here and
you know I love that and it's good to
see that from a fan perspective because
I I was a fan and I'm a fan of this
organization before I'm a player.
>> And then finally, you played with a
great quarterback up in Buffalo and and
now you come in here to play with a
young quarterback that's ascending, you
know, uh how important was it in your
decision to get back to Washington
knowing that there is a franchise
caliber quarterback in the building?
>> You can't go to the playoffs without a
quarterback. You know, that's one thing
that I embodied, you know, over the last
o over my absence years here. But, you
know, a quarterback can get you as far
as you want them to go. You know, the
team just helps them.
>> Okay. All right. Welcome back, man.
>> Thank you so much.
>> All right. Appreciate it, Tim.